A Finding Aid to the Erwin Panofsky Papers, 1904-1990 (bulk dates 1920-1968), in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Correspondence, 1921-1978, undated; Series 1; Archival Resource Key; (Boxes 1-16; 16 linear ft. Reels 2108-2128)
  - Colleagues, Scholars, Students and Other Individuals, 1921-1978, undated; 1.1; Archival Resource Key
    - Klesse - Koch, 1948-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 12)
      Klesse, Brigitte
      Klessmann, Rüdiger
      Klibansky, Raymond
      Knapp-Fisher, J. S.
      Koch, Rev. Alfred
    - Koch, Robert Alan, 1949-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Koehler - Köhler, 1938-1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 14)
      Koehler, Wilhelm and Margarete, 1942-1959
      Koepplin, Dieter, 1963
      Köhler, Wolfgang, 1938-1961
    - Kossoff - Koyré, 1952-1963, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 15)
      Kossoff, Florence S.
      Koyré, Alexandre
    - Kracauer - Kraft, 1941-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 16)
      Kracauer, Siegfried
      Kraft, Konrad
    - Krautheimer, Richard, 1938-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 17-18)
    - Krönig, Wolfgang, 1950-1958; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Kristeller, Paul Oskar, 1947-1976, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Kubler, George, 1936-1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Kuhn - Kultermann, 1939-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 22)
      Kuhn, Charles L.
      Kultermann, Udo
    - Künstsler - Kurz, 1953-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 23)
      Künstsler, Gustav
      Kupferberg, C. A.
      Kurz, Otto
    - Ladenburg - Lynes (single letters), 1929-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 24)
      Ladenberg, Mrs. Rudolf
      Ladendorf, Heinz
      Laging, Duard W.
      La Marre, John
      Lambert, Phyllis B.
      Landan, Julie
      Lantham, Richard
      Laporte, Paul M.
      Lapp, John C.
      Latte, K.
      Laufer, June
      Laurier, Mrs. Jacques De
      Lawall, David E.
      Leary, Eleanor W.
      Lehmann, Paul
      Lennon, William
      Leonhardt, Leo
      Lering, Antoine
      Lesley, Everett P., Jr.
      Lexow, Jan Hendrick
      Leynen, Hilde
      Leyritz, Gabariel Chaneaux de
      Li, Chu-tsing
      Linardos, Ilialna
      Lilienfeld, Karl
      Lincoln, Carolyn R.
      Lindroth, Sten
      Lindsay, Kenneth C.
      Lisco, Karen
      Lissim, Simon
      Lowey, Alice
      London News
      Loomis, Roger S.
      Lowry, Bates
      Lucas, S.
      Luce, Robert
      Ludden, Franklin Monroe
      Lumb, E. Sue
      Lyon, Quinter M.
      Lynes, Mildred C. (Mrs. Russell Lynes)
    - Lachmann, Claire, 1957-1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Ladner, Gerhard B., 1952-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Lafond - Lankheit, 1942-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 27)
      Lafond, Jean
      Lamarre, John H.
      Lambert, Phyllis
      Lanckorónska, Countess Maria
      Landsberger, Franz
      Lang, Renée B.
      Langer, William L.
      Lankheit, Klaus
    - Larrabee - Laurvik, 1940-1951; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 28)
      Larrabee, Harold A.
      Larrabee, Stephen A.
      Laurvik, J. N.
    - Lauts - Lavalleye, 1950-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 29)
      Lauts, Jan
      Lavalleye, Jan
    - Lavin, Irving and Marilyn, 1950-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Lawrence - Lee, 1936-1966, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 31)
      Lawrence, Marion
      Lawrence, Sidney
      Leadbeatter, Dorothy
      Leake, Chauncey D.
      Lederer, Wolfgang
      Lee, Paul A.
    - Lee, Rensselaer Wright, 1938-1967, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Leeper, John, 1959-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Lehmann, Karl, 1927-1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Lehman, Phyllis W., 1947-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Lehman - Leroquais, 1940-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 36)
      Lehman, Robert
      Lehamnn-Haupt, Hellmut
      Lejeune, Jean
      Lenneberg, Edith
      Lerici, Carlo M.
      Leroquais, Victor
    - Levey - Levin, 1949-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 37)
      Levey, Michael
      Levin, Harry T.
    - Lewine, Milton J., 1964-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Lewis, Wilmarth S., 1959-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Liebeschütz - Loomis, 1953-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 1)
      Liebeschütz, Hans
      Lieftnick, G. I.
      Linder, Harold F.
      Loeschcke, Walter
      Lohamm-Siems, Isa
      Loomis, Laura H.
    - Lopez - Lossky, 1950-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 2)
      Lopez, Robert S.
      Lord, Eileen A.
      Lord, L. E.
      Loshak, David
      Lossky, Boris
    - Lotz, Wolfgang, 1954-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Lowe, E. A., 1940-1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Lowinsky, Edward E., 1943-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 5-8)
    - Ludwig - Lyna, 1947-1959, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 9)
      Ludwig, Allan
      Lyna, Frederic, undated
    - Mc/Mac, General (single letters, McCarthy - McNulty [Mc and Mac interfiled]), 1941-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 10)
      McCarthy, Joseph L.
      McElhinney, Alice L.
      MacGreevy, Thomas
      McKinnis, Fred L.
      MacLagan, Eric
      McNamee, Father Maurice
      McNulty, J. Bard
    - McCall, John E., 1939-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - McCormick, Thomas J., Jr., circa 1951-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 12-13)
    - MacCracken - McMahon, 1944-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 14)
      MacCracken, R. A.
      McGee, Anne
      McGrath, Robert L.
      McGuire, William
      McKechwie, Margaret
      McKenzie, A. Dean
      McKibbin, David
      McMahon, A. Phillip
    - M, General (single letters, Magallón - Mylonas), 1932-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 15-16)
      Magallón, Don Tomás
      Magnuson, Torgil
      Malkiel, Jakow
      Maltese, Corrado
      Mandelbaum, Maruice
      Mango, Cyril
      Maniates, Maria Rika
      Manuel, Fritzie
      Mar, André de la
      Marabottini, Alessandrom
      Marazza, Achille
      Marchand, Hans
      Marck, Jan H. M. van der
      Marg, W.
      Marichal, Robert
      Markham, Anne
      Marks, Peter
      Marrow, James
      Martens, Bela
      Martin, William E.
      Martin, Y.
      Martone, Father Thomas
      Marruach, Acisclo
      Masi, Alessandro de
      Mattingly, J. R.
      Mayekawa, Seiro
      Mayer, Martin
      Mendel, Arthur
      Merlen, L. Jacobs van
      Merkel
      Merle, Pierre
      Messerer, Wilhelm
      Metternich, Franz Graf Wolff
      Meurer, Heribert
      Meyer, Ann Mans
      Meyer, Erich
      Meyer, Herman
      Meyer-Baer, Kathi
      Meyers, Hans
      Millar, Bradford P.
      Miller, Charles R. D.
      Miller, Clyde R.
      Misch, Georg
      Moehle, Ruediger
      Moeller, Kurt
      Molle, F. Van
      Mondadori, Alberto
      Montagna, Lino
      Montago, Jennifer
      Montesquiou Frzensac, Blaise de
      Montone, Father
      Moratz, Frank
      Morawitz, Kurt
      Morris, Dudley H.
      Morse, Beverly
      Mortimer, Mary H.
      Moseley, Jane E.
      Moulinier, Edward P.
      Müller, Gerhard
      Mullet, Charles F.
      Munhall, Edgar J.
      Münzel, B.H.M.
      Mutsaers, B.
      Mylonas, George E.
    - Maas - Manasse, 1955-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 17)
      Maas, John C.
      Mabille, A.
      Mack-Smith, Denis
      Mahon, Denis
      Majno, Guido
      Malone, Lee
      Manasse, Ernst Moritz
    - Mandowsky - Martin, 1925-1968, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 18)
      Mandowsky, Erna
      Mann, Alfred
      Marcus, Stanley
      Marenau, Henry
      Marquand, Eleanor C.
      Marsden, C. A.
      Martens, Bella
      Martin, F. David
    - Martin, John Rupert, 1952-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Martin - Meeson, 1947-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 20)
      Martin, Kurt
      Mather, Frank J., Jr.
      Mayo, Penelope C.
      Mayor, A. Hyatt
      Meeson, B.
    - Meiss, Millard, 1936-1975, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 21-24)
    - Melamed - Mendel, 1950-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 25)
      Melamed, Hope Goodman
      Meller, P. Peter
      Meltzoff, Stanley
      Menase, Luc
    - Menil - Meyerson, 1952-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 26)
      Menil, John de
      Merritt, Benjamin
      Mertz, Richard R.
      Metzger, Mendel
      Meyerson, I.
    - Meyne - Middledorf, 1944-1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 27)
      Meyne, Willi
      Middledorf, Ulrich
    - Miner, Dorothy Eugenia, 1935-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Minott - Mitchell, 1957-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 29)
      Minott, Charles I.
      Mirimonde, A. P. de
      Mirsky, Jeannette
      Mitchell, Charles
    - Mitrany, David, 1952-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Moakley, Gertrude, 1955-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Modestini - Möhle, 1957-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 32)
      Modestini, Mario
      Möhle, Hans
    - Möller, Lise Lotte, 1954-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Mommsen - Morey, 1942-1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 1)
      Mommsen, Theodor E.
      Mongan, Agnes
      Mink, Samuel H.
      Morey, Charles Rufus
    - Morley - Mosse, 1947-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 2)
      Morley, S. Griswold
      Morper, Johann Joseph
      Morse, Marston
      Mortimer, M. H.
      Mosse, Walter
    - Mueller - Mufmord, 1951-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 3)
      Mueller, Earl
      Müller, Theodor
      Müller, Wolfgang J.
      Müller Hofstede, Cornelius
      Mumford, Lewis
    - Muraro, Michelangelo, 1956-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Mütherich, Florentine, 1960-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - N, General (single letters, Nachod - Nostrand), 1937-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 6)
      Nachod, Frederick C.
      Najder, Zdzislaw
      Nathan, Otto
      Nauert, Charles G., Jr.
      Neisser, H.
      Nemser, Cindy
      Neuberger, Hans
      Neumann, Sigmund
      New York Times
      Newton, Francis J.
      Nicely, Katharine
      Nickerson, Hoffman
      Nicolson, L. Vertova
      Nicolson, Mary Coe
      Nilgren, Ursula
      Nill, Anna M.
      Niver, Charles
      Norden, Heinz
      Nostrand, Albert Van
    - Nadel - Nef, 1944-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 7)
      Nadel, George H.
      Nahm, Milton C.
      Nash, Ray
      Nathan, Hans
      Nathan, Helmuth
      Nef, John U.
    - Negri - Neumann, 1936-1971, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 8)
      Negri, Enrico and Lilo de
      Nesselhauf, Herbert, undated
      Neugebauer, Otto
      Neumann, Jaromír
    - Neumeyer, Alfred, 1943-1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Newton - Nock, 1948-1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 10)
      Newton, Caroline
      Nicolson, Marjorie H.
      Nock, Arthur D.
    - Nordenfalk, Carl, 1939-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 11-15)
    - Nordström - Norton, 1953-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 16)
      Nordström, Carl-Otto
      Nordström, Folke
      Norton, Paul F.
    - O, General (single letters, O'Brien - Opie), 1933-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 17)
      O'Brien, Gerard F.
      O'Dea, Connie
      Oelher, Lisa
      Oertal, Robert
      Offenbacher, Emil
      Oksala, P.
      Olin, Caroline Bower
      Opie, J. N. Lindsay
    - Oberer - Ong, 1931-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 18)
      Oberer, Hariolf
      O'Connell, Rev. John P.
      Oexmann, Theophila Joan
      Offner, Richard
      Ong, Rev. Father Walter J.
    - Oppenheimer, 1956-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 19)
      Oppenheimer, Fritz E.
      Oppenheimer, J. Robert
    - Orsini, Gian, 1954-1966, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Osten, Gert van, 1952-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 21-22)
    - Owen, Henry G., 1956-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - P, General (single letters, Paine - Pulitzer), 1937-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 24)
      Paine, Francisca Warren
      Paine, Michael J.
      Palacios, Alvar Gonzalez
      Palmer, George A.
      Pancoast, John
      Papajewski, Helmut
      Pargellis, Stanley
      Park, Marion S.
      Parker, Harry S., III
      Parsons, Harold W.
      Partington, Ruth
      Paul, Jurgen
      Pauwels, H.
      Pawson, Herbert B.
      Pevsner, Nikolaus
      Philippe, Joseph
      Philippsohn, Jenny
      Picard, Charles
      Picard, Raymond
      Pierson, Mrs. Emery Lancaster
      Pinthus, Alexander
      Poillon, Mrs. Arthur
      Polier, Justine Wise
      Polzer, Joseph
      Pompanin, A.
      Poole, Dewitt Clinton
      Popesco, Paul
      Post, Chandler R.
      Preddy, C. R., Jr.
      Price, Derek J.
      Price, Pamela
      Princeton Club of New York
      Prudential Insurance Company
      Puhst, Johann
      Pulitzer, Joseph
    - Paatz - Pächt, 1951-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 25)
      Paatz, W.
      Pächt, Otto
    - Pais - Papp, 1953-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 26)
      Pais, Abraham
      Palme, Per
      Panofsky, Hans and Wolfgang
      Papp, Béla
    - Parkhurst, Charles P., 1943-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Pásztory, Catherine, 1949-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Pauli, 1928-1970, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 29)
      Pauli, Gustav
      Pauli, Magdalene
      Pauli, Wolfgang
    - Paulsson, Gregor, 1952-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Pacchiai - Petersen, 1947-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 31)
      Pacchiai, Pió
      Pedretti, Carlo
      Peery, William
      Perlmutter, Joshua
      Perrig, Alexander, F. X.
      Petersen, Ulla
    - Peyre - Phillips, 1949-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 32)
      Peyre, Henri M.
      Pfeiffer, H.
      Philip, Lotte Brandt
      Philippot, Paul
      Phillips, John
    - Pichetto - Plaut, 1948-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 1)
      Pichetto, Stephen G.
      Pieper, Paul
      Piper, Otto A.
      Placzek, George
      Plaut, Alfred
    - Plochmann - Pope-Hennessy, 1938-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 2)
      Plochmann, George Kimball
      Pobor, Grga
      Poggioli, Renato
      Pölnitz, Gerhard Freiherr von
      Pope-Hennessy, John
    - Porcher, Jean, 1947-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Posner - Puyvelde, 1942-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 4)
      Posner, Donald
      Post, Gaines
      Pratt, Robert A.
      Pressouyre, Léon
      Preston, Lionel
      Procacci, Ugo
      Puppi, Lionello
      Puyvelde, Leo van
    - Quarré - Qvarnström, 1946-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 5)
      Quarré, Pierre
      Quintavalle, Augusta G.
      Quirt, Walter W.
      Qvarnström, Gunnar
    - R, General (single letters, Rabuse - Ryskamp), 1938-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 6)
      Rabuse, Georg
      Radernaher, Hans
      Rakob, Friederich
      Rappolt, Paul
      Rasmussen, Nils Ludvig
      Rand, E. K.
      Reading, Carolyn
      Reed, Sue Welsh
      Reibnitz, Rudolf V.
      Reincke, Heinrich
      Reissner, H. G.
      Reimche, Jean
      Revel, E.
      Reynal, Eugene
      RIAS
      Richter, George M.
      Richter, Gisela M. A.
      Rieck, Wilhelm
      Riedl, Peter Anselm
      Rieth,, Adolf
      Riggio, Conrad F.
      Ringbom, Sixten
      Ringler, Josef
      Ritter, Ewald
      Robinson, Chalfant
      Rodríguez Savall, Alfonso
      Roems, H.
      Rose, Elsa
      Rood, Sherrill M.
      Rookmaaker, H. R.
      Roosen-Runge, H.
      Rorimer, James J.
      Rosenbach, A. S.
      Rosenbaum, Elizabeth
      Rosenberg, C. G.
      Rosenberg, Frances
      Rosenbert, Mr. and Mrs. John
      Rosenfeld, Leonard J.
      Rosenthal, Jane
      Ross, James Bruce
      Ross, Lawrence J.
      Roth, Cecil
      Rowley, George
      Rubin, Enid
      Rückert, Ranier
      Raudruf, L.
      Ruhemann, Helmut
      Rutan, Clinton N.
      Ryskamp, Charles
    - Rabb - Raemisch, 1949-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 7)
      Rabb, Theodore K.
      Rabinowicz, Theodore
      Rademacher, Hans
      Raemisch, Waldemar
    - Raggio, Olga, 1951-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Randall - Raubitschek, 1940-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 9)
      Randall, Lewis V.
      Randall, Lillian M. C.
      Raubitschek, Antony E.
    - Rawson - Reff, 1951-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 10)
      Rawson, C. J.
      Reese, Gustav
      Reff, Theodore
    - Regteren - Reinhold, 1945-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 11)
      Regteren Altena, J. Q. van
      Reinhart, Oskar
      Reinheldt, Curt
      Reinhold, H. A.
    - Reti, Ladislao, 1957-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Reutersvärd, 1957-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 13)
      Reutersvärd, Oscar
      Reutersvärd, Patrick
    - Rewald - Richter, 1937-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 14)
      Rewald, John
      Reynolds, Robert L.
      Reznicek, E.K.J.
      Richelson, Paul W.
      Richmond, Donald E.
      Richter, Irma A.
    - Rickert - Robb, 1936-1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 15)
      Rickert, Margaret
      Ripley,Elisabeth
      Robb, David M.
    - Roberts - Roosval, 1946-1967, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 16)
      Roberts, R. M.
      Robertson, Giles
      Roche, Thomas P., Jr.
      Roe, Albert
      Romanini, Angiola Maria
      Roosval, Johnny
    - Rosen - Rosenberg, 1954-1967, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 17)
      Rosen, Edward
      Rosenau-Carmi, Helen
      Rosenbaum, Allen
      Rosenberg, J. B.
    - Rosenberg, Jakob, 1943-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Rosenberg - Rosenthal, 1946-1962, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 19)
      Rosenberg, Pierre
      Rosenblum, Robert
      Rosenthal, Erwin
      Rosenthal, Gertrude
    - Rosenwald, Lessing J., 1951-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Röthel, Hans K., 1932-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Rothlein - Röthlisberger, 1952-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 22)
      Rothlein, Jerome
      Röthlisberger, Marcel
    - Rowland - Ruzicka, 1948-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 23)
      Rowland, Benjamin
      Rudenstine, Angelica
      Rudzinski, Aleksander Witold
      Russell, Heide
      Rüstow, Alexander
      Ruzicka, R.
    - S, General (single letters, Saalman - Silvers), 1937-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 24)
      Saalman, Howard
      Saint-Aubain, M. P. de
      Salaquarda, Charles
      Sales, Grover, Jr.
      Salinger, Gerhard
      Salm, Christian Altgraf
      Salomon, Albert
      Sandbla, Nils G.
      Sanders, Ernst H.
      Sanders, Gabe
      Sanford, Eva Matthews
      Savage, H. L.
      Scheidmantelivian J.
      Schelldorfer, K.
      Scher, Stephen K.
      Schickel, Richard
      Schildt-Bunim, M.
      Schmalenbach, Fritz
      Schmidt, Georg
      Schmidt, H. D.
      Schmidt-Degener, H.
      Schneider, Donald D.
      Scholtens, H.J.J.
      Schrader, Jack L.
      Schramm, Percy Ernst
      Schreinert Kurt
      Schrickel, H. G.
      Schubert, Wolf H.
      Schuchhardt, W. H.
      Schütt, Mary
      Schütze, Martin
      Schultz, H. Stefan
      Schulz, Juergen
      Carl Schurz Memorial Foundation
      Schwartz, Gary
      Schwartz, James H.
      Secchi, Claudio Cesare
      [Sessions?], Roger
      Shearman, John K. G.
      Siebenhüner, H.
      Siegel, Eli
      Siegerist, Henry E.
      Silvers, Ilse Folk
    - S, General (single letters, Silverstein - Szathmary), 1944-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 25)
      Silverstein, Mary
      Silz, Priscilla
      Simon, Erika
      Simor, George
      Singleton, Charles S.
      Sinicins, N.
      Sjöqvist, Erik
      Slingenberg
      Sloane, John P.
      Smith, Francis P.
      Smith, Graham
      Smith, Nancy R.
      Smith, Richard Flanders
      Smulders, F.
      Snyers, M. R.
      Snyder, Robert
      Solomon, Dagmar I.
      Solomon, Eva aTevan
      Solomonski, Fritz
      Spear, Richard E.
      Spector, Jack
      Speigel, Eileen
      Sptizer, Wolfgang
      Stampflel, Felice
      Stange, Alfred
      Stapleforth, Richard W.
      Stebbins, Frederick A.
      Steinhausen, H. K.
      Stern, Frederic A.
      Stern, Otto
      Sternfeld, W.
      Stevens, Charles Rolfe
      Stewart, Dorothy N.
      Stites, Raymond S.
      Stoessel, Oskar
      Stone, I. F.
      Strauss, Walter L.
      Strayer, Joseph R.
      Strong, Earl D.
      Strunsky, Robert
      Sulzberger, Susanne
      Sztuki, Pa stwowe Zbiory
      Szablowski, Jerzy
      Szathmary, Arthur
    - Sachs - Salas, 1948-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 26)
      Sachs, Curt
      Sachs, David
      Sachs, Paul J.
      Saffaro, Lucio
      Salas, Xavier de
    - Saldern - Salmi, 1940-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 27)
      Saldern, Axel von
      Salinger, Herman
      Salmi, Mario
    - Salomon, Richard, 1934-1968, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Reel 28-31)
    - Santillana - Saran, 1956-1967, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 32)
      Santillana, Giurio de
      Santos, Reynaldo dos
      Saran, Bernhard
    - Sarollli - Sarton, 1946-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 33)
      Sarolli, Gian Roberto
      Sarton, George
    - Sauerländer, Willibald, 1957-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Sauerlandt - Scaglia, 1921-1969, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 1)
      Sauerlandt, Max
      Saxl, Fritz
      Scaglia, Gustina
    - Schaefer, Claude, 1947-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Schaper, Gunter, 1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Schapiro, Meyer, 1937-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Schaut, Father Quentin L., 1948-1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 5-6)
    - Schefold - Schiff, 1958-1972, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 7)
      Schefold, Marianne, 1958-1965
      Schéle, Sune, 1962
      Schenk zu Schweinsberg, Eberhard Freiherr
      Schiff, Gert
    - Schilling - Schönberger, 1945-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 8)
      Schilling, E.
      Schilling, Rosy
      Schlunk, Helmut
      Schmid, Wolfgang
      Schmidt, Gerhard
      Schönberger, G.
    - Schöne, Wolfgang, 1954-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Schrade - Schuchhardt, 1927-1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 10)
      Schrade, Hubert
      Schramm, Ruth
      Schryver, Antoine de
    - Schulz-Behrend - Schwabacher, 1954-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 11)
      Schulz-Behrend, George
      Schürer-von Witzleben, Elisabeth
      Schüssler, Hermann
      Schwabacher, Willy
    - Schwarz, 1953-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 12)
      Schwarz, Heinrich
      Schwarz, Henry F.
    - Schwarzenberg - Seidlin, 1946-1966, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 13)
      Schwarzenberg, Erkinger
      Schweitzer, Bernhard
      Segall, Berta
      Seidlin, Oskar
    - Selig - Serra, 1947-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 14)
      Selig, Karl Ludwig
      Seligmann, Germain
      Serra, Manuel
    - Sessions - Setton, 1950-1967, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 15)